1. openBrowser(URL)
5. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Home Page/header_digibox"))
9. click(findTestObject("Registration/icon-acount"))
13. setText(findTestObject("Registration/field-account"), "agungpriyadi")
17. setText(findTestObject("Registration/field-Password"), "Laskar123456")
21. click(findTestObject("Login/btn-sign in"))
25. click(findTestObject("Registration/icon-acount"))
29. click(findTestObject("Address Management/Shipping Address/btn_My Address"))
33. click(findTestObject("Address Management/Shipping Address/btn_Delete"))
37. waitForElementClickable(findTestObject("Address Management/Shipping Address/button_OK"), 10)
41. btnOK = new com.kms.katalon.core.testobject.TestObject()
45. btnOK.addProperty("xpath", EQUALS, "//div[contains(@class,'el-message-box')]//span[normalize-space()='OK']")
49. waitForElementVisible(btnOK, 10)
53. okElement = findWebElement(btnOK, 10)
57. executeJavaScript("arguments[0].click();", Arrays.asList(okElement))
61. refresh()
65. waitForPageLoad(10)
69. deletedEmail = new com.kms.katalon.core.testobject.TestObject()
73. deletedEmail.addProperty("xpath", EQUALS, "//*[contains(text(),'agung.priyadi@gtech.digital')]")
77. takeScreenshot()
81. closeBrowser()